Charlie Seemann collection of photographs of vaqueros and gauchos
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Uruguay photographs, September 1986, 138 slides: color; 35mm
  - Castrating calf, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_073 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho with cattle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_074 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho with cattle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_075 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho with cattle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_076 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho with cattle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_077 (Box 2)
  - Horse with gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_078 (Box 2)
  - Fence, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_079 (Box 2)
  - Stone fence post, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_080 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho roping calf, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_081 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho roping calves, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_082 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho roping calves, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_083 (Box 2)
  - Gauchos examining braided leather work, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_084 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho rolling cigarette, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_085 (Box 2)
  - Interior of bunkhouse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_086 (Box 2)
  - Hacienda sun room, Estancia Los Morteros, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_087 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_088 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_089 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_090 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_091 (Box 2)
  - Asada, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_092 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_093 (Box 2)
  - Pasture, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_094 (Box 2)
  - Drum used by musicians, Estancia Los Morteros, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_095 (Box 2)
  - John Manness, Patron of Estancia Los Morteros, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_096 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_097 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_098 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_099 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_100 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_101 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_102 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_103 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_104 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_105 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_106 (Box 2)
  - Demonstration of putting together the gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_107 (Box 2)
  - Charlie Seemann with Dr. Roberto de Olano and Patricia Gill, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_108 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_109 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho saddle completed, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_110 (Box 2)
  - Charlie Seemann playing with Uruguayan musicians, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_111 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_112 (Box 2)
  - Demonstrating gaucho saddle, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_113 (Box 2)
  - Showing saddle blanket, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_114 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho, horse, and dog, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_115 (Box 2)
  - Holding saddle with cinch, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_116 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_117 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_118 (Box 2)
  - Breaking horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_119 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho roping, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_120 (Box 2)
  - Castrating calves, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_121 (Box 2)
  - Castrating calves, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_122 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho chasing cow, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_123 (Box 2)
  - Castrating calves, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_124 (Box 2)
  - "La linea," lining up horses before the day's work, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_125 (Box 2)
  - "La linea," lining up horses before the day's work, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_126 (Box 2)
  - Boy on horse, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_127 (Box 2)
  - Tapestry in hacienda, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_128 (Box 2)
  - Andres Gallinal, patron of Estancia San Pedro de Timote, Cerro Colorado, giving tour of sheep shearing barn, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_129 (Box 2)
  - Sheep shearing barn, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_130 (Box 2)
  - Mounted gauchos, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_131 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_132 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho with dogs, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_133 (Box 2)
  - Gauchos with sheep, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_134 (Box 2)
  - Sheep, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_135 (Box 2)
  - Sheep, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_136 (Box 2)
  - Hacienda, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_137 (Box 2)
  - Gaucho, September 1986, AFC 2018/001: u_138 (Box 2)
- Series 4: Brazil photographs, November 1986, 60 slides: color; 35mm
  - Horses and gaúchos at Bagé, Brazil, gaúcho festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_001 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos in Bagé, festival parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_002 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_003 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos preparing to join parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_004 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_005 (Box 2)
  - Musician playing at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_006 (Box 2)
  - Musicians playing at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_007 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho performing spur dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_008 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho with flag in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_009 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_010 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_011 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_012 (Box 2)
  - Dancers at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_013 (Box 2)
  - Landscape, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_014 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_015 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_016 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_017 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_018 (Box 2)
  - Musicians at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_019 (Box 2)
  - Race track in Bagé, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_020 (Box 2)
  - Guitarist at race track, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_021 (Box 2)
  - Race track in Bagé, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_022 (Box 2)
  - Race track in Bagé, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_023 (Box 2)
  - Race track in Bagé, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_024 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at dance/dinner, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_025 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho in parade, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_026 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho in parade joking around with friends, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_027 (Box 2)
  - Tack/supply room, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_028 (Box 2)
  - Young attendees at dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_029 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_030 (Box 2)
  - Musicians at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_031 (Box 2)
  - Mounted gaúchos lined up on horseback for outdoor mass, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_032 (Box 2)
  - Race track in Bagé, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_033 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho with traditional "facón" or knife, in belt, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_034 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_035 (Box 2)
  - Priest celebrating outdoor mass, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_036 (Box 2)
  - Young couple dressed for the dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_037 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_038 (Box 2)
  - Horses head with tack, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_039 (Box 2)
  - Saddled horse at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_040 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_041 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_042 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at asada, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_043 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at asada, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_044 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at asada, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_045 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival drinking maté, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_046 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_047 (Box 2)
  - Charlie Seemann with gaúchos at dance after they dressed him in gaúcho attire, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_048 (Box 2)
  - Dancer's feet with spurs, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_049 (Box 2)
  - Elder highly respected gaúcho in hotel, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_050 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho in parade joking around with friends, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_051 (Box 2)
  - Mounted gaúchos lined up on horseback for outdoor mass, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_052 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_053 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_054 (Box 2)
  - Gaúchos at festival, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_055 (Box 2)
  - Gaúcho at festival drinking maté, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_056 (Box 2)
  - Couple going to dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_057 (Box 2)
  - Couple going to dance, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_058 (Box 2)
  - Bar, or pulperia, interior, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_059 (Box 2)
  - Couple dancing, November 1986, AFC 2018/001: b_060 (Box 2)